>> Jem Young: 好的，大家都很自信，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Okay,
everybody's looking confident,
这就意味着你可能已经做到了
that means you're probably done.
或者你错了，你有个打字号，你还不知道。
Or you're wrong and you have a typo and
you don't know it yet.
我们会很快发现的
We'll find out real fast.
那就让我们继续吧
So let's go ahead and run that.
所以，如果我们只运行节点 simpleServer.js，
So if we just run node simpleServer.js,
which I already did here,
节点 simpleServer.js >> Jem Young: And
node simpleServer.js
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
在您的 Web 浏览器中，仅点
in your web browser, just point yourself
端口 8080上的本地主机。
to your local host on port 8080.
>> Jem Young: 你应该看到这样的东西，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: You should see
something that looks like this,
让我把它炸掉
let me blow that up a bit.
我的书签正在显示。
My bookmarks are showing.
您 >> Jem Young: 没有任何内容。
You
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Nothing to it.
我不应该说，当涉及工程学的时候，我尽量不讲简单，或者
I shouldn't say that, when it comes to
engineering I try not to say simple, or
这很简单因为那是相对的
it's easy,
because that's totally relative.
如果你不明白它会让你感到难过
And then if you don't get
it makes you feel bad.
但这是我能想到的最简单的服务器。
But this is the simplest
server I could think of.
可能有人在外面写一个集会，那也不是
There's probably someone out there who
can write one assembly, well it's not
技术上更简单也许稍快一点也不重要
technically simpler, probably
slightly faster, it doesn't matter.
但关键是什么都可以成为服务器。
But the point is anything can be a server.
我们可以用各种语言为服务器提供脚本
And we can script a server
in every language,
每个 Web 语言都有一个写服务器的方法。
every web language there's
a way to write a server.
我们回去看看我们在这里做什么
Let's go back and
see what are we doing here.
我们正在做的是在节点上，我们正在导入 http 库。
What we're doing is we're in node,
we're importing the http library.
然后 http 具有创建服务器的能力，我们只会写
And then http has this ability to create
a server, and we're just gonna write
到输出，响应，我们将写 " Hello World" 。
to the output, to the response,
we're gonna writes Hello World.
我们在港口 8080 上收听
And we're listening on port 8080.
我们正在设置一个控制台，让您知道服务器已启动并且
And we're setting a console just to
let you know that the server is up and
一旦我们拿到了它就跑了
running once we get it going.
您将使用的每个单节点服务器的基本信息
The basics of every single node
server you're ever gonna use
此调用返回请求响应。
is this call back with request response.
可能是，您可能会使用承诺，您可以使用异步等待，但是
It may be, you might use promises,
you might use async await, but
总会有要求回应的
there's always gonna be request response.
第三个参数通常是下一个，用于
And the third parameter is usually next,
which is used for
在您要执行此请求时创建中间件，并且
creating middleware when you're
saying do this request and
然后通过这些中间件进行传递，然后进行响应。
then pass it through these middleware and
then respond.
但在这种情况下，我们并不是用这种方式，而是熟悉这个模式。
But in this case, we're not using any of
that, but be familiar with this pattern.
我可能不会太投入，还有其他的 Frontoo Masters'
I probably won't get too much into it,
there are other Frontend Masters'
更深入的课程，更细致的课程，更深入的程度，
courses which go much, mush deeper into
note servers, much more granular level,
我们待会儿再考虑
and we'll think those out later.
但一般来说这都是要求回应的
But in general it's always
going to be request response,
这就是你写的每台单节点服务器的基本模式
that's the basic pattern to every
single nodes server you'll ever write.
我们在监听一个任意的港口它可能是港口
And we're listening on an arbitrary port,
it could be port,
我不知道 6304 甚至 6305 也不重要
I don't know 6304 or
even 6305, it doesn't matter.
一般下面的端口想说 1000 是保留的，所以
Generally ports below want
to say 1000 are reserved, so
因特网在端口 80 上运行，在  上，因特网在端口上运行，任何人吗 ?
the internet runs over Port 80, on HTTPS,
the Internet runs over port, anybody?
>> 扬声器 2: 443 >> Jem Young: 是， 443，是，非常好。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: 443
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes, 443, yes, very good.
有保留的港口的概念
There's this concept of reserved ports and
pretty much
1000 以下的任何内容都可能被某些程序或语言保留。
anything below 1000 is probably
reserved by some program or language.
所以你不想和那些人乱搞
So you don't want to mess with those, but
选择任意高的数字 ( 如端口 8080 ) 通常非常安全。
choosing an arbitrarily high number
like port 8080 is usually pretty safe.
我们在 localhost中，我也可以输入，这只是 127.0.0.1的速记。
And we're in localhost, I can also type,
that's just shorthand for 127.0.0.1.
哎呀我在跑 Nginx[ LAUGH] 我在跑 Nginx
Whoops, am I running Nginx,
[LAUGH] I am running Nginx.
通常 127.0.0.1 是回送命令。
Usually 127.0.0.1 is a loopback command.
只是说不出去上网打港口的服务器
It's just saying instead of going out to
the Internet and hitting a server on port
8080我要在 8080上打我的 localhost
8080, I'm just gonna hit my
localhost running important at 8080.
我有 Nginx 从不同的配置中运行
I have Nginx running from
a different configuration.
别担心你什么都没看见就假装没发生
Don't worry about that you didn't see
anything, just pretend that didn't happen.
但一般来说，当你跑的时候，做地方发展，
But generally, when you're running,
doing local development,
你总是会打你的 localhost
you're always gonna hit your localhost.
如果进行远程开发，那么可以命中远程主机，而这就是服务器。
If you do remote development, you can
hit remote host, and that's a server.
或者如果你想知道我是怎么做的，我把它放进来了，但是
Or if you're wondering how I did the line
numbers, I put it in the notes here, but
对他们很有好处
in them it's good to try that.
我要杀了这个命令
And I'm just gonna kill this command.
看看你是否想展示路线号码我打了 Esc
See if you wanna show the line
number oops, I hit Esc,
最后一个线路节点我说集合号
last line node, and I'll say set number.
我觉得这是对的，对，感谢我的行号。
I think that's right, yes,
thanks to my line number.
>> Jem Young: 如果我想隐藏他们，我想再说一次。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And if I want to hide them,
I think say set number again.
噢，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不
Oops, nope, no number.
我喜欢这个简单的说重点
I like that, it's simple, to the point.
设置无数字和 [INAUDIBLE]，仅在个案中设置。
Set no number and
[INAUDIBLE], just in case.
我不想做任何你想做的事情他是怎么做到的
I'm not trying to do anything that
you're like, well, how did he do that?
我想让你知道我所知道的一切除了我对快速和
I want you to know everything I know,
except my in depth knowledge of Fast and
疯狂的特里维那是我的
Furious trivia, that's mine.
没有其他人可以这么做
No one else can have that.
>> Jem Young:
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And right clear.
>> Jem Young: 那个服务器，最简单的，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: That server,
let's the simplest,
裸机服务器创建应用程序的方式。
bare bones way of creating an application.
或者像 Sam 说的那样，是回应要求的东西。
Or, like Sam said,
something that responds to requests.
直说吧我们能搞定的
Pretty straightforward,
we can handle this.
现在我们要更先进的了这就是简单的
And now we're going to get much more
advanced this is this is as simple
就像它一样
as it gets.
现在，我们要加快速度。
And now we're going to pick
up a little bit of speed.
我们说的是规模上的服务器
We're talking about servers at scale,
因为很明显我无法在我的笔记本上运行 frontendmasters.com
because obviously I can't run
frontendmasters.com on my laptop.
我也许能，实际上你会感到惊讶的是
I probably could, actually you'd be
surprised that how efficient servers
现在是这样，但这并不是个好主意。
are now, but it's really not a good idea.
它变得更复杂我们会讨论并发症
It gets more complicated,
which we'll talk about the complications,
这就是我们来这里的原因
that's why we're here.
如果服务器这么简单，那么每个人都是完全同步的工程师。
If servers were this simple,
everybody would be full sync engineer.
但是在这些服务器上，它们的启动非常简单，非常简单。
[LAUGH] But they start off really,
really simple, as far as these servers go.